Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Welcome to the Black Market.
Now, I won't lie, it may be a bit on the dangerous side, but they've got some crazy good magic items here.
Damn it! Lost again!
Too bad for you, I can see the future, dearie.
That old bat really cleaned me out.
I guess I shouldn't be gambling anyway.
Well, huh?
Whoa, not bad.
Ha-ha! The Black Market can be quite dangerous. It's no place for such delicate flowers to roam about.
Be gone with you, insect.
Hey! Check this out, it's the best thing ever!
Ha-ha?
No! Him again?!
Hey, I remember you!
Ha-ha! That's Seke! Ha-ha!
How've you been, ha-ha?
I told you my name is, ha-ha! No, I mean it's Seke!
Who's this?
We took the entrance exam together.
Oh, so you're on the Mantis Squad.
The best looking women here and there with him?!
Hold on. They're wearing Black Bull's robes too?!
Stupid Asta!
I can't believe I'm actually jealous of a Black Bull!
Damn him!
That runs the whole reason I wound up in the praying mantises in the first place!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'll make him pay!
ha-ha!
He looks mad as ...
He sees that money around 11 times 11 times.
Cap-4
Hey, He gets maybe one more thing?
Not for any actions could ever run for.
I agree!
わかってるんだ
縦横未尽にどこまでも
幅かけたらな
いつの日も夢見てた
それでも一歩一歩しかしかな
世界でも何度も香り立てそう
本能のまま諦めしたいからさ
遥か未来へ今駆け出したんだ
未だ見ぬ不安すらすべて超えて
あの日へ描いた
僕が僕であるために
いつの日だ
ページの続けが来よう
君のよう希望と
まるでいつかのワンページのような
君と僕ら出会えた
これよくせきって呼ぼうか
ugal美での女性さたに
あの日く頭に行きている
ページの Hearts
すべておまり変えする
instead i hear the bulls are 30 stars in the red stars oh yeah that reminds me we got a star from
the wizard king on our very first mission awesome huh no way he must be kidding and you worked hard
for it right they're actually serious no calm down wow did you really i guess you're doing okay huh
how about you huh that's second and i'll have you know i now have two starfish
no get back here those are my winnings you fiend give them back to me
the old bat from before
he's got a lot of nerves snatching someone's purse in front of a group of magic knights you can say
that again just leave this to the kiddo he's got it covered i hope you're right dear
yes aha asta i'm not going to let you have all the glory ron's creation magic seki shooting star
ew yuck oh gross oh don't worry i'll handle this you three ladies just sit back and let seki do his
thing i think you can catch me not a chance you're not getting away
ah who's there whoops sorry about time he gave up no way i'm letting you go that easy well a stubborn one
oh i can't see
i'm gonna get that purse back this kid's even faster than i thought if he's catching up to me on foot
the only way i'll catch him is if i do something about that cloud it's a good thing it's made of magic
here you really think some sword's gonna slice through my bandit's cloud witch
yeah i've got you now
huh huh huh this purse snatcher is mine man that is so cool
you're done now and i'll get the credit
is that i'm so sick of that stupid laugh if i'm gonna go then so are you
oh no what happened
he got me the thief had a poisoned blade hang in there stay strong
huh huh am i dying i had such high aspirations i thought someday i would
i hate to leave things to this idiot but
you managed to best me during the exam it may be over for me but it's not for you
you i hereby bequeath you my dreams
maybe this isn't such a bad way to go
no wait say something
uh-huh why am i still alive
hey what was that for huh listen up you can't just give your dreams away
keep on living and make them come true yourself don't you give up so easily
honestly honestly something like this is hardly going to kill you
it's nothing more than a temporary irritant a quick dab of chic ointment and you'll be just fine
haha you'll have to work hard if you want to be ready for our next meeting asta bye for now
haha later haha our little bull may look like a kid compared to that mantis but he's much more
powerful where it truly counts
try not to let anyone else steal this
thank you very much for all your help sir magic knight see you around granny
be careful out there stay out of trouble thank you again magic knights
a sword that nullifies spells you know my life i've never once seen magic like that before
actually can it even be considered magic
the army certainly nabbed himself an intriguing new member this is why my secret excursions are so
necessary
finally there you are uh-oh what are you up to now really sir
well since you asked i'm wandering the castle town in disguise hoping to stumble on new magic but
sir that's not appropriate for a man of your position encountering new magic is a rare and
precious thing even so i never know what magical mysteries might be awaiting me please listen you
incorrigible magic geek now marks no need to get so worked up oh is that the fresh face over in william's
squad
excellent timing it seems i have yet another new magic to meet don't worry i won't be long
don't you dare sir
one of the golden dawn's newest members
you know the gifted youth sought after by every squad captain at the magic knight's entrance exam
and the squad's other newcomer the royal mimosa vermilion
mission their first mission acting as escort for selim de hapshass
the son of the noble congressman hapshass and we are to accompany him to the heart kingdom but why
you're familiar with congressman hapshass only with his name
i've heard he's considered a bit of an upstart it doesn't seem he's very well thought of
which gives him additional reason to worry about bandit attacks on his son as the lad sets off to
study abroad in the heart kingdom wouldn't you think yes but surely the hapshass family has plenty
of powerful magic users in their employ it seems he'll only rest easy if his son is guarded by members
of a well-known magic knight squad the congressman is quite generous in his annual donations to the magic
knights coffers and serving government officials is part of our duty any objections no none sir
carry out any mission you are given the good of the clover kingdom must always be our priority
yes of course sir take mimosa with you as well accompanied by their teacher those two should be
sufficient look after our fledglings class dismissed
salim de hapshass lost to you know in the final portion of the entrance exam as a result he wasn't
offered a place on any magic knight squad what reason could he have for choosing you know to be his
bodyguard i'm so excited to be going on my first mission klaus you know we're in this together right
right right hush mimosa stay sharp oh yes you as well of course cheeky little newcomer
so you know tell me how have you been
i hope you're not wearing that scary face because of me
i chose you as my escort because i wanted the opportunity to apologize to you
you're hoping to be the wizard king one day yes
i am but how did you know all the captains raised their hands you could have joined any squad
and you chose to become a member of the golden dawn i knew then that you must have ambitions
i've seen how talented you are enough successes behind you and before long you'll be a household
name throughout the kingdom you know of the four leaf clover grimoire sound good
your dream of being the wizard king make it come true someday i'll be able to brag to my children
about our first meeting believe it or not kids i once fought the wizard king i'll tell them
wow daddy really they'll say you're amazing we still have some time before we reach the heart kingdom
if you don't mind perhaps you could tell me about yourself though if you'd rather not that's all right
i'm from a small village called hajj
yes i've heard of it before a commoner village on the edge of nowhere isn't that where the legend of
the first wizard king defeating the demon and saving the world originated it's not just a legend in fact
the demon's giant skeleton is still there oh the village is all i've known i was abandoned outside the
church when i was a baby i've never seen my parents faces i have no idea who they are the church was
small and quite poor but the priest and the nun who worked there racist the best they could i'm very
grateful clear so far still there must be someone in the hapshast family who can use transportation
magic why go to all this trouble and with us as his only escorts if there were a legitimate threat of
bandit attacks why wouldn't they increase the security detail this mission is one mystery after
another odd indeed there's something so eerie about it i'll go take a look
hey you can't just guard up mimosa um yes sir
you know defend salim that's the basic plan
so
gotcha
uh
whoa
Oh, my!
Fantastic, Yuno!
Interesting.
It didn't seem like they were coming for Salim.
Well done.
You really saved me back there.
So efficiently, too.
Impressive.
I didn't even have to cast my Holy Lightning Rising Salim spell.
My interest in you is thoroughly piqued.
Wait, I have an idea.
Why don't we pay a quick visit to that village of yours?
It would be fascinating to see where you were raised.
I wonder if perhaps it was the environment you grew up in that made you so powerful.
Pardon, sir, but that would require quite a detour.
Also, the risk.
As we've just seen, we don't know what's in store for us.
Now, please, let's make straight for the hard key.
It doesn't matter who might attack us, because I have the three of you to protect me, right?
Well, yes, of course, sir.
But still, a noble visiting a commoner's village.
Oh, please, we're only stopping by.
Yes, sir.
Besides, after so long away, Yuna must be eager to see everyone from the church again, right?
That's really none of your concern.
Now, now.
Oh, look at that.
The skeleton, I take it?
Well, it's certainly large.
And I assume that statue standing on its head is of the first wizard king?
How fascinating.
Now then, where will we find your church?
Just over there.
Oh, my!
Yuna!
Welcome back!
Hi, sister.
Just look at how much you've grown!
I haven't changed.
How different can I look after only two months?
There is something, though.
Let's see.
Yes, your face, that's it.
You look more grown up now.
So what brings you here?
A mission.
We're just stopping briefly.
How did I let myself get dragged to this backwater village?
Oh, um, hello there.
My name is Sister Lily.
I am with Captain Vonschens' Magic Knight Squad, the Great Golden Dawn.
Klaus Thrunetz, in charge of the newcomer's education.
Klaus!
Yes, of course.
I recognize your name from Yuna's letters.
It's so nice to meet you.
Thank you for everything you've done for him.
Letters?
What exactly did you say about me?
Hmm.
I see.
Hi!
I'm Mimosa.
I joined the squad with Yuna.
Yes.
I've heard about you, too.
Oh, you have?
What have you been writing about me, Yuna?
Hmm.
Goodness.
What a beautiful sight.
Huh?
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I am Salim de Hapshass, son of the noble congressman Hapshass, and Hapshass family heir.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Really, such a pleasure.
Ah!
I'm so sorry, sir.
No, no.
It's quite all right.
Truly.
Yuna!
It's Yuna!
Our dear boy is back!
It's so good to see you!
How's it going?
You look good.
Oh, wow.
Check it out.
A golden dawn robe.
It's the real deal.
Yuna's back!
Yay!
Hey, what about Asta?
Yeah, Asta!
Yes, of course.
Have you been keeping in touch with him?
I haven't.
Are you going to stay the whole night here?
You will, won't you?
Um, well...
Afraid not.
Our visit will be quick.
We have a time-sensitive mission to complete.
Aw!
Come now, Klaus.
We're not in that much of a rush to be off, are we?
Surely it wouldn't be difficult to spare an hour.
But, sir...
Perfect!
Well, then, this calls for a Hajj feast.
Pot potatoes for everybody!
What do you think?
Sounds good, huh?
Please, make yourselves at home.
Come on in.
Thank you.
What a marvelous church you have.
I don't think I've ever seen one this tiny before.
It's so adorable.
Adorable?
Almost like a children's playhouse.
Brr!
You have to tell us all about the Magic Knights, Yuna.
Yeah, tell us!
Tell us!
How did I let myself get dragged to some shabby church?
僕は眩しくて目を閉じる。
散々考えた革命は手の中におかしいだろう。
笑いたければ笑えばいいから。
残された僕らはなにかになりたくて。
I'm going to be the same morning
I'm going to choose the next day
I'm going to be the same day
CLOP pluck!
Sekei's HA HA! Lesson Part Two
Wait we're doing this again?
OF COURSE! What did you expect?
There's a great deal more work to be done
if you wish to attain Ha HA-Hood
Your shooting star is totally awesome
I'm glad someone appreciates it
Well... yeah especially that thing on the front
So coooooool
You're getting closer to ha-ha-hood.
I see now. That's what ha-ha is.
Yes! Now you too are ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Are all men such idiots?
Damn that Yuno. Such an impertinent newcomer.
He had better learn to respect his superiors or I will be held responsible for my actions.
Black Clover, page 13. The Wizard King saw. Continued.
My magic is never giving up!